<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ultramarine</string>

    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About us</string>
    <string name="nav_products">Products</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="dark_mode">Dark Mode</string>
    <string name="light_mode">Light Mode</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>

    <string name="about_subtitle_1">The Beginning</string>
    <string name="about_desc_1">In 1835, José María Gurtubay, a Bilbao merchant, made a mistake in his order to his suppliers. He wrote "Envíenme primer barco que toque puerto de Bilbao 100 o 120 bacaladas primera superior". However, the "o" was misinterpreted as a 0, and instead of receiving 100 or 120 cods, he received **1,000,120**! This unexpected surplus of cod became the staple food for the people of Bilbao during the summer of that year, leading to the creation of many recipes.</string>

    <string name="about_subtitle_2">The Tradition Continues</string>
    <string name="about_desc_2">In the following decades, bacalao became an essential ingredient in traditional Bilbao cuisine, and bacaladerías (dried cod shops) became a common sight in the cities streets and squares. Bilbao and cod were forever linked.</string>

    <string name="about_subtitle_3">Gregorio Martín: A Visionary Entrepreneur</string>
    <string name="about_desc_3">In 1931, Gregorio Martín, a young entrepreneur from Medina del Campo, opened his own business in Artecalle 22, Bilbao. Thanks to his friendship with an importer, Gregorio innovated his business by specializing in bacalao and placed a sign that read: "Gregorio Martín. Especialidad en bacalao remojado todos los días. Tno.- 13.707". This marked the beginning of "La Bacalada" de Artecalle, a business that would become a staple in Bilbao culinary scene.</string>

    <string name="about_subtitle_4">Our Story Today</string>
    <string name="about_desc_4">Today, at Gregorio Martín, we continue to offer the same high-quality products, including enormous cods, bulk legumes, cheeses, cured meats, preserves, wines, condiments, and chocolates. Our secret lies in the origin of our products and the personalized service our employees have provided for decades.</string>

    <string name="about_subtitle_5">Our Goal</string>
    <string name="about_desc_5">We aim to continue providing the best products at the best prices, while maintaining our authenticity and professionalism. We believe that our personalized service and high-quality products set us apart, and we are proud to be a reference point in Bilbao culinary scene.</string>

    <string name="home_text_1">Since 1931, we have been specialists in cod, legumes, cheeses, cured meats, preserves, wines, condiments, chocolates…</string>
    <string name="home_text_2">One of our secrets is that we are lovers of high-quality gastronomy at Ultramarinos Gregorio Martín.\n Our years of experience combined with high-quality raw materials is the perfect combination for a 5-star product.</string>
    <string name="home_text_3">Featured products</string>

    <string name="products_all">All categories</string>
    <string name="products_fish">Fish</string>
    <string name="products_legumes">Legumes</string>
    <string name="products_preserves">Preserves</string>

    <string name="default_web_client_id">786401790212-bpq7k8b71h3egvf6eovnr5fugde0lvja.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
</resources>